hkticketing.com 2019-03-30

# HK TICKETING

**1\. Statement of Policy**

Hong Kong Ticketing ("HK Ticketing") recognizes and understands that customers and website visitors are concerned about the privacy of information. HK Ticketing pledges to comply with the requirements of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance (Cap.486) of the Laws of Hong Kong.

When we collect personal data from individuals, we will provide them with a Personal Information Collection Statement ("PICS") on or before the collection in an appropriate format and manner.

 **2\. Collection of Information**

You may be invited to provide to your personal data on HK Ticketing's website for different purposes at different times. If you are under the age of 18, you should obtain consent from your parent or guardian before you provide HK Ticketing with your personal data.

 **3\. Statement of Practice**

Your personal information collected and held by us will be used for the purposes of creating and maintain your membership account, processing your booking orders, ticket purchase, course enrolment, transactions, enquiries, feedback, newsletter subscription or contacting you when necessary.

We will not provide your personal data to third parties for direct marketing or other unrelated purposes without your consent.

 **4\. Kinds of Personal Data Held**

For handling booking orders, ticket purchase, course enrolment, enquiry and feedback, subscription via HK Ticketing website, ticketing counters/outlets and booking hotline, your personal details, including name, title, gender, contact information such as your telephone number, mailing address, email address, company name, IP address, geographic location, your credit card and billing information, including name of credit cardholder, credit card number, billing address, credit card expiry date and credit card verification code, additional necessary information such as “Name on Ticket”, your relevant identification like membership numbers as registered in other organization (if any) as required by the relevant course providers/event organizers to process your booking/enrolment, are collected and held by HK Ticketing.

 **5\. Main Purposes of Collecting and Keeping Personal Data**

HK Ticketing may use the personal data you provided for any of the following purposes:

  1. to create and maintain your membership account;
  2. to process your ticket bookings and purchase, course enrolment, transactions at HK Ticketing, and producing your own history record;
  3. to handle and respond to your enquiry and feedback and to contact you when necessary; and
  4. to handle your newsletter subscription, to maintain the subscription record and to send newsletters and other materials to you.

HK Ticketing may from time to time use aggregate non-identifying information about our customers to better design our website and/or to improve our services and products. We may need to provide this information to third parties. However, this information will never identify any single user in particular.

Except specified in this Privacy Policy Statement, we will not intentionally use or share the personal data you provide to use in ways unrelated to the aforementioned purposes without your prior consent.

 **6\. Information Collected When You Visit Our Websites**

 _Use of Cookies and other Tracking Mechanisms_

When you visit HK Ticketing’s website, the servers of HK Ticketing will only collect data relating to your visits (including but not limited to your location, IP address, browser type, domain name and access time) to manage and improve the design of the website but will not collect your personal data. We may use cookies and other tracking mechanisms described below to track information about your use of HK Ticketing’s website. We may combine this information with other personal information we collect from you to better serve you and/or maintain your information across multiple pages within or across one or more sessions. 

Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computers, mobile phones or other devices through your web browser for record-keeping purposes. Some cookies allow us to make it easier for you to navigate HK Ticketing’s website and enable a faster log-in process.

We may also engage third parties to track and analyse non-personally identifiable data from the website. We use the data collected by such third parties to help us administer and improve the quality of HK Ticketing’s website and to analyse usage of the same. Such third parties may combine the information that we provide about you with other information that they have collected. You can edit your browser settings to disable cookies but to do so you may not be able to utilize certain functionality of the website(s) of HK Ticketing.

We may also collect information regarding your IP address, browser type, domain name and access time. This information is used for HK Ticketing’s research purposes. This is unrelated to and separate from your personal data. In rare instances, IP addresses may be used to assist in deterring and/or preventing abusive or criminal activity on the website.

 _Statistics on visitors to our websites_

When you visit our website we will record your visit only as a “hit”. The webserver makes a record of your visit that includes your IP addresses (and domain names), the types and configurations of browsers, language settings, geo-locations, operating systems, previous sites visited, and time/durations and the pages visited (visitor data). We use the visitor data for the purpose of maintaining and improving our websites such as to determine the optimal screen resolution, which pages have been most frequently visited etc. We use such data only for website enhancement and optimisation purposes. We do not use, and have no intention to use the visitor data to personally identify anyone. 

**7\. Accuracy of Information**

You may be requested to provide to HK Ticketing certain personal data (particularly relating to your contact information) for specific services. If you fail to provide or update accurate information as requested for each specific service, the provision of such services by HK Ticketing may be affected.

 **8\. Outsourcing Arrangements**

HK Ticketing’s internal IT system is developed and maintained by in-house staff and an overseas third-party service provider. The third-party service provider does not have access to personal data stored in the IT system except when it is carrying out trouble-shooting on the system at HK Ticketing office under the supervision of HK Ticketing staff.

The HK Ticketing website and booking engine are developed and maintained by an overseas third-party service provider. All HK Ticketing service providers are bound by contractual duty to keep confidential any data they come into contact with against unauthorised access, use and retention.

 **9\. Our Commitment to Personal Data Security**

HK Ticketing takes appropriate steps to protect the personal data we hold against loss, unauthorised access, use, modification or disclosure.

To prevent unauthorised access and ensure the correct use of the personal information we collect, HK Ticketing has implemented appropriate physical, technical, and administrative measures to safeguard and secure the personal data we collect.

We use industry standard practices to protect the personal information we collect. For example, we use encryption, firewalls and Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology to protect in transmission the personal data we collect online. When you type in sensitive information such as credit card details, it will be automatically converted into codes before being securely transmitted by the Internet. 

HK Ticketing protects the personal information we collect in a secure database with important information being encrypted. The database servers are hosted in a protected data centre with appropriate access controls. 

When disposing of personal data, paper documents containing personal data are securely destroyed, and electronic files storing personal data are permanently deleted.

Notwithstanding the foregoing, no data transmission over the internet or any other public network can be guaranteed to be completely secure, and privacy cannot be assured in your communications to us. You are encouraged to protect against unauthorized access to your password. You are advised to sign out from your account when finished particularly when using a shared computer.

 **10\. Disclosure of Personal Data**

The personal information we collect about you will not be disclosed by us to any other party without your prior consent. 

Where permitted by applicable local law, we may also disclose your personal data to third parties: (i) when required by law, by court order, or in response to a search warrant or other legally valid inquiry; (ii) to an investigative body; (iii) to enforce our agreements with you; (iv) with your express consent, or, (vi) pursuant to our good faith belief that disclosure is required by law or otherwise necessary to the establishment of legal claims or defences, to obtain legal advice, to exercise and defend our legal rights, to protect our rights or property and those of our subsidiaries or associated companies, or to protect the life, body or property of an individual. This also applies when we have reason to believe that disclosing the personal data is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.

 **11\. Retention of Information**

HK Ticketing will retain your personal data for a period no longer than necessary for the fulfillment of the purposes for which they are or are to be used. If you are a subscriber of HK Ticketing services, your personal data will be retained for a reasonable period after termination of your subscription for verification and audit purposes. Different retention periods apply to the various kinds of personal data collected and held by HK Ticketing in accordance with policies in standing instructions and administration manuals. The above is subject to any legal, statutory, regulatory or accounting requirements. 

**12\. Third Party Websites**

The website of HK Ticketing may from time to time contain linkages to other websites. These other websites are independent from the website of HK Ticketing. HK Ticketing has no control or management over the contents of such other websites or their privacy policies or compliance with the law. You should be fully aware that the provisions of such links do not constitute an endorsement, approval, or any form of association by or with HK Ticketing. HK Ticketing has no control over your personal data submitted by you, if any, to other websites. This Privacy Policy Statement only applies to the website of HK Ticketing. You should read the respective privacy policies of other websites.

 **13\. Notice on Direct Marketing**

Occasionally, we may use your personal data (including your name and contact details) to send you marketing communications such as emails containing news, offers, promotions and joint marketing offers. 

We cannot use your personal data unless we have received your consent or indication of no objection.

or

You can opt-out from receiving marketing communications at any time, free of charge, by:

  1. following the opt-out instructions contained in the communications;
  2. login your HK TICKETING “MY Account” for [unsubsciption](https://premier.hkticketing.com/Membership/Unsubscribe.aspx);

You can indicate your consent by providing us with your personal data through the Subscription Form on our website, ticking boxes indicating your consent on [here](https://premier.hkticketing.com/Membership/UpdateAccountPreferences.aspx) or

You can opt-out from receiving marketing communications at any time, free of charge, by:

  1. following the opt-out instructions contained in the communications;
  2. login your HK TICKETING “MY Account” for [Unsubsciption](https://premier.hkticketing.com/Membership/Unsubscribe.aspx); 

**14\. Access and Correction of Information and Withdrawal of Consent**

You have the right to request in writing to the Communications Manager of HK Ticketing:

  1. for access to your personal data held by HK Ticketing (if any);
  2. require HK Ticketing to correct your personal data that is inaccurate (if any); and
  3. withdraw your consent to the use of your personal data (such withdrawal may, however, affect our services to you).

All such requests will be handled promptly in accordance with the requirements of the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance. HK Ticketing may charge a reasonable fee for processing your data access request.

 **15\. Account Cancellation**

If you want to cancel your HK Ticketing account, please contact HK Ticketing Customer Service at accountcancellation@hkticketing.com, marked “Account Cancellation”, and we shall handle your request immediately. The subject account will be cancelled and your personal data will be removed within fourteen (14) business days after our receipt of the request in writing. Please ensure that all relevant event/performance (i.e. the event/performance for which tickets have been purchased under the subject account) under the subject account has ended before sending us your request of Account Cancellation. We are not able to contact you in case of any change of cancellation/rescheduling of such relevant event/performance once we have cancelled the subject account.

 **16\. Change of Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy Statement may from time to time be updated, revised and changed. Any change, update or modification will be effective immediately upon being posted on website of HK Ticketing. You are advised to check it on a regular basis.

 **17\. Change of Control**

If the ownership of certain business of HK Ticketing changes, HK Ticketing may need to transfer your personal data to the new owner of such business so the new owner may continue to operate the business subject to the condition that the new owner shall make use of your personal data in accordance with this Privacy Policy Statement. You will be notified of such transfer and you may decide to withdraw your consent to the use of your personal data.

 **18\. Enquiries**

Any enquiries regarding personal data privacy policy and practice, please contact the Communications Manager of HK Ticketing at:

Hong Kong Convention and Exhibition Centre (Management) Limited

1 Expo Drive, Wanchai  
Hong Kong  
Attn.:  
Communications Manager, Hong Kong Ticketing  
(Marked Confidential)

, or by email at [privacy@hkticketing.com](mailto:privacy@hkticketing.com)

 **19\. English Version**

If there is any inconsistency or conflict between the English and Chinese version of this Privacy Policy Statement, the English version shall prevail.

**Transaction**

Information collected under the Hong Kong Ticketing ("HK Ticketing") Membership Registration Form and Payment Transaction Form, which includes your name, title, phone number, email address, mailing address, credit card and billing information(i.e. name of credit cardholder, credit card number, billing address, credit card expiry date and credit card verification code) will only be used for the purpose of creating and maintaining your membership account; processing your course enrolment, ticket purchase and bookings, transactions at HK Ticketing and producing your own history record.

Please note that it is mandatory for you to provide personal data marked with asterisks. In the event that you do not provide such personal data, we may not be able to provide you with our services or process the registration of HK Ticketing’s membership, course enrolment, ticket purchase, bookings and transactions.

The personal information we collect about you will not be disclosed by us to any other party without your prior consent.

The personal information you submit will be encrypted (a secure means of transmission) when it is sent electronically to us.

 **Newsletter subscription**

Information collected under the Newsletters and Alerts section of the Hong Kong Ticketing ("HK Ticketing") My Account, which includes your name, email address will only be used for the purpose of handling subscription of HK Ticketing newsletter, maintaining the subscription record and sending newsletters and other materials to you .

Please note that it is mandatory for you to provide personal data marked with asterisks. In the event that you do not provide such personal data, we may not be able to provide you with our services or process your subscription.

The information collected by means of cookies on this website about you will be used only for compiling aggregate statistics on how visitors browse the website. Such statistics are collected for the purpose of managing and improving the design of the website.

 **Enquiries and Feedback**

Information collected under the “Customer Feedback Form ” and “Sell Event Tickets Through Us Form” of Hong Kong Ticketing (“HK Ticketing”), which includes your name, company name, phone number, IP address and email address will only be used for the purpose of handling your enquiries and feedback and contacting you when necessary.

Please note that it is mandatory for you to provide personal data marked with asterisks. In the event that you do not provide such personal data, we may not be able to provide you with our services or process your enquiries and feedback and to contact you.

The personal information we collect about you will not be disclosed by us to any other party without your prior consent.

The personal information you submit will be encrypted (a secure means of transmission) when it is sent electronically to us.

To update your personal details or request access to your personal data, please 

  1. Login your HK Ticketing “My Account” for information and correction of your personal data;
  2. or contact Communications Manager of HK Ticketing at

Hong Kong Convention and Exhibition Centre (Management) Limited  
1 Expo Drive, Wanchai  
Hong Kong  
Attn.: Communications Manager, Hong Kong Ticketing  
(marked Confidential)

, or by email at [privacy@hkticketing.com](mailto:privacy@hkticketing.com) (marked Confidential)

You can find out more about our policy of personal data protection by accessing HK Ticketing Privacy Policy Statement available at [Privacy Policy](https://premier.hkticketing.com/Content/buyers/privacy.aspx).

If there is any inconsistency or conflict between the English and Chinese version of this Statement, the English version shall prevail.
